<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QuotesApi</string>
    <string name="upgrade">Welcome to the Quotes App Upgrade!\n\nUnlock Premium Features\n\nUpgrade now to unlock exclusive features and enhance your quote browsing experience.\n\nPremium Features Include:\n\nAd-Free Experience: Enjoy uninterrupted browsing with zero advertisements.\n\nUnlimited Favorites: Save as many quotes as you want without any restrictions.\n\nCustomizable Themes: Personalize your app with a variety of beautiful themes.\n\nDaily Quote Notifications: Receive inspirational quotes daily to uplift your spirits.\n\nOffline Access: Access your favorite quotes even without an internet connection.\n\nWhy Upgrade?\n\nEnhanced Experience: Get rid of distractions and immerse yourself in a seamless browsing experience.\n\nSupport Development: By upgrading, you support the continuous improvement and maintenance of the Quotes App.\n\nUpgrade Now\n\nUnlock premium features for only $X.XX per month and elevate your quote journey to the next level.</string>
    <string name="feature">Welcome to QuoteMaster – the ultimate app designed to elevate your daily routine with a curated collection of wisdom, motivation, and inspiration! Whether you seek a spark of creativity, a dose of motivation, or simply a moment of reflection, QuoteMaster is your go-to companion.\n\nDiscover Limitless Inspiration:\nExplore a vast library of handpicked quotes from renowned thinkers, authors, leaders, and celebrities spanning across various categories such as love, life, success, happiness, and more. With daily updates and fresh content, there’s always something new to discover and inspire you.\n\nPersonalized Experience:\nTailor QuoteMaster to your preferences with customizable settings. Favorite the quotes that resonate with you the most, create personalized collections, and set up daily reminders to receive your dose of inspiration at the perfect time.\n\nSeamless Sharing:\nSpread positivity and wisdom effortlessly with QuoteMaster’s easy sharing feature. Share your favorite quotes with friends, family, and social networks to inspire those around you and spark meaningful conversations.\n\nEnhanced Accessibility:\nQuoteMaster is designed for convenience and accessibility. Enjoy a user-friendly interface that makes browsing, saving, and sharing quotes a breeze. Whether you’re on your smartphone, tablet, or desktop, QuoteMaster adapts seamlessly to your device.</string>
    <string name="community">\"Quotables: Where Words Inspire, Connect, and Resonate.\"\n\n\"Unlocking Wisdom, One Quote at a Time.\"\n\n\"Words That Bind: Building Bridges Through Quotes.\"\n\n\"Echoes of Insight: Where Every Quote Tells a Story.\"\n\n\"Quotidian: Where Daily Quotes Fuel Inspiration.\"\n\n\"Inspire, Share, Repeat: The Power of Quotations.\"\n\n\"Quotiverse: Where Every Quote Finds its Home.\"\n\n\"From Thought to Quote: Uniting Minds Across the Globe.\"\n\n\"Quotient: Where Words Multiply Inspiration.\"\n\n\"Quotopia: Where Ideas Converge and Quotes Flourish.\"\n\n\n\n\n\n</string>
</resources>